(English Subtitle) Growing.Pains.S01E13 -= The.Love.Song.of.M.Aaron.Seaver =- Subripped by zerox
好了，只剩下两天时间练习
Okay, now, we've only got two days left to practice...
我们要让凯罗好好提高
so we've all gotta help Carol work on her gutter ball.
为什么？她已经每次都能下沟了
But why, Dad? It's perfect. It goes in the gutter every time.
来吧，凯罗试试看
Come on, Carol, now et's try this release.
假如球朝沟的方向滚去，怎么办？
So suppose it's headed for the gutter. Now what do we do?
身子左倾，把球扳回来
We lean to the left here and pull her back to the right.
拉回右边
Over to the right.
太好了
Perfect.
大家振作!
Come on, guys, get it together.
今年要把库斯曼家打个落花流水
We gotta kill the Koosmans this year.
本，用不着杀气腾腾的
Now, Ben, this is a neighborly little game of tenpins.
只不过是保龄球友谊赛
et's not turn it into "Bowling for Blood."
爸爸，他们连续三年击败我们了
Dad, they've beaten us three years in a row.
而且小肯尼.库斯曼还站在我们家窗外.
And then little Kenny Koosman stands outside our window...
嚷个不停
and does that stupid little chant.
“猪猴狗兔，龙蛇马羊，打球都比西弗家强”
"Turkeys, monkeys, chipmunks, beavers: they all bowl better than the Seavers! "
-确实要杀个片甲不留! -咱杀!
- Well, let's kill the Koosmans. - Let's kill the Koosmans.
-来吗，麦姬 -准备好了没？
- Come on, Maggie. We can do it. - Okay. Ready?
-杰森，瞧我的 -好样的!
- Okay, Jason, watch this. - Attagirl.
姿势不对要告诉我
Tell me if I'm doing it right.
-慢慢来 -好吧.
- Take your time. - Okay, and....
-发球不错 -这个.
- Good bounce. - Oh, that....
右边，右边.
To the right.
我们是不会输的
Oh, well, hey, how can we lose?
因为我们有秘密武器“西弗球王”
We've got our new secret weapon, Mike "The Strike" Seaver.
-平均得分187 -太好了
- Yeah. You know, his average is up to 187. - Oh, good.
他回来了
There he is now.
我们赢定了!
We're number one!
好，来吧
Okay, here we go.
-大家小心点，我来了 -好
- Okay, watch carefully. Here we go. - All right.
谢谢大家
Yes, thank you, thank you.
我还有一件事.
And now there's just one more thing I'd like to say:
凯罗，给你3块 帮我写一首新象征主义的诗
Carol, I'll give you $3 if you write me a neo-symbolist poem.
麦克.
Mike...
干嘛要让妹妹写一首新象征主义的诗？
why would you want your sister to write you a neo-symbolist poem?
今天在学校里遇到天大的喜事了
Dad, the most wonderful thing happened to me at school today.
麦克？
Mike?
说到哪里了？对了
I forgot what I was gonna say. Oh, okay.
麦克
Mike.
能否回答里面大海的意义？
Can you explain for us the significance of the sea in Moby Dick?
可以，可以
Sure. Sure.
就是比小海和中海更大的海
It's the letter between the "l" and the "K."
这是我在教师会议上学到的
It's a little technique I picked up at the last teachers" convention.
大家安静
Okay, people, settle down.
大家好，我叫朱丽叶
Hello. I'm Juliet.
我叫罗密欧
And I'm Romeo.
爸爸，我从没见过像朱丽叶这样的女孩
Dad, I've never met a girl like Juliet before.
麦克，你每次都这样说
Mike, you say that every time.
这次是不同的，朱丽叶并非庸脂俗粉
Well, it's different this time, Dad. I mean, Juliet is really classy.
她在巴黎出生，在伦敦和纽约长大
Dad, she was born in Paris. She was raised in London and New York.
她会写诗，还会说3种语言
She writes poetry, and she even speaks three different languages.
那比你多说3种了
That's three more than you speak.
所以要弄首诗在她面前卖弄？
So you want to impress this new girl with a poem?
不是普通的诗，要是新象征派的诗
Yeah, but not just any poem, Dad, a neo-symbolist poem.
这是她最喜欢的流派
That's her favorite brand.
凯罗写的话就是凯罗的诗 不是你的
Mike, if Carol writes the poem, it's not yours, it's Carols.
她给我就是我的了
Not if she gives it to me.
麦克，若是要跟那姑娘交朋友.
Well, Mike, if you're really going to get along with this girl...
必须赤诚相见，千万别弄虚作假
sooner or later you're gonna have to be straightforward with her.
爸爸，这是不行的
Dad, I can't do that.
干嘛不行？通常你会怎么勾搭女孩？
Oh, sure you can. What do you usually say to a girl you like?
“宝贝，想要去天堂的单程车票吗？”
"Hey, baby, want a one-way ticket to paradise? "
-我还是帮他写一首吧 -好极了
- I'd better write him the poem. - All right!
麦克
Mike.
我知道你们是怎么想的.
Hey, look. I know what you guys are thinking...
不过我还是要这首诗作为敲门砖 然后我就自力更生
but I'm just gonna use this poem to get her to talk to me. Then I'll be myself.
好吧，如果你们认为.
Well, if you guys think that a $3 poem is any substitute...
坦诚只值3块钱的话，那随便
for real and honest communication, then go ahead.
麦克，爸爸说得对
Mike, Dad's right.
坦诚至少值5块钱
Real and honest is gonna cost you $5.
“目光扫视前方”
"With eyes that scan the distance
“双脚在沙滩上”
"With feet that cross the sand
“浮想联翩..”
"With thoughts that keep me dreaming
“呆呆矗立..”
"This place is where I stand
“我恨母亲”
"I hate my mother."
朱丽叶，好诗!
Way to write, Juliet!
真是好诗!
Hey, was that a poem or what, guys?
谢谢，朱丽叶
Thank you, Juliet.
还有谁想要念诗？
Does anyone else have anything they'd like to read for the class?
老师，我也有一首诗要朗诵
Miss Jeffress, I have a little poem I'd kind of like to recite for the class today.
不是那种会让我被炒鱿鱼的吧？
This isn't gonna get me fired, is it?
老师，人说.
Miss Jeffress, you know how they always say...
教师是最辛苦的园丁.
that despite all the hardships of teaching...
栽培的是国家的栋梁
there are those rare moments that make it all worthwhile?
嗯
Yes.
这是送给你的
This ones for you.
“你我二人走吧”
"Let us go then, you and l
“夜色晶莹，像一只拍扁的苍蝇”
"When the evening is spread out like a swatted fly
“生命中充满瘴气，充斥着原胶质”
"Life being miasmic, somewhat protoplasmic
“雨淋漓..”
"What does it matter if raindrops pitter-patter
“使得街上光怪陆离”
"Like loose pancake batter on the griddle of our days?
“但愿、我是一双丝袜，耷拉着无牵无挂”
"I should have been a pair of pantyhose hanging on the shower rod of our dreams."
麦克，写得真棒
Michael. That was incredible.
是吗？
Oh, really?
这只是我的小作品
I mean, it was really one of my minor works.
在现代文化的底蕴中.
I found it to be a fascinating parodic melding...
渗透着一种诙谐的韵味.
of popular culture and the lyrical mode.
是啊？正是!
Yeah, yeah, that's it!
终于遇到知音了
God, it is so nice to be understood.
麦克，原来你这么有才华，太好了
You know, Michael, it's wonderful to discover how gifted you are...
我第一印象还以为.
because for some reason I got the impression...
你只是一个乡巴佬
that you we're just another suburban dolt.
我？乡巴佬？
Me? A suburban dolt?
人生真是讽刺
Life can be cruelly ironic, can't it, Juliet?
才华洋溢.
All that...
英俊潇洒
and cute, too.
朱丽叶马上就要来了
Okay, now Juliet's gonna be here any minute.
大家快读读这些东西
Now, there's a few little things here I'd like to go over.
-这是什么？ -我们家的简史
- What's this? - It's a brief family history.
大家快点背下来
Now, if you guys can just quickly commit this to memory.
-麦克 -妈，怎么了？
- Mike. - Yeah, Mom?
这里说我是作家
It says here that I'm a writer.
你是啊
Oh, well, you are, Mom.
刚写完第27本小说
And that I've just completed my 27th novel.
对，这只是初步统计
Okay, all right, so it was a rough estimate.
我成画家了
Apparently, I'm a painter.
爸爸，无可否认.
Well, you gotta admit, Dad...
厕所的油漆是你涂上去的
you did a pretty bang-up job on that upstairs bathroom.
而我是.
And I'm a child....
是神童
Prodigy, Ben.
对，我告诉朱丽叶.
Yeah, Ben, see, I just told Juliet that you we're sort of a....
你是某种哲学奇才
Well, that you we're a genius at philosophy.
当我这样打眼色时.
So whenever I wink at you like this...
你就念一句这些话
I want you to read one of these little phrases here.
好的，试试看
All right, et's try one.
-我思故我在 -很好
- "I think, therefore I am." - Good, good.
麦克，荒谬!
Mike, this is ridiculous.
麦克，你真的要我们这样子对待朱丽叶
Mike, you don't seriously expect us to tell Juliet that we're all these things.
拜托，我只是在你们脸上贴金
Come on, Mom, I'm just trying to make you guys look good.
谢谢你了
Oh, I appreciate that, Mike...
你这是要我们撒谎
but you're asking us to lie.
而且是骗不了人的谎
And, badly.
就今天一晚，忍耐点
Come on, guys. Just for tonight, bear with me.
如果在关键时刻连家人都不可靠.
Look, if you can't count on your family at a crucial moment in your life...
那还有谁可靠？
who can you count on?
-朱丽叶 -米克
- Juliet. - Mikhail.
当年就应该取这么个名字
To think we came that close to naming him that in the first place.
爸爸，妈妈，这是朱丽叶
Mom, Dad, this is Juliet.
-朱丽叶，这是我爸爸妈妈 -朱丽叶，你好
- Juliet, these are my parents. - Hello, Juliet.
米克常常谈起你们
Mikhail has told me so much about you.
看来你们的人生都很精彩
It sounds like you have a fascinating life.
人生是什么？
Yes, but what is life?
9岁就能说出这么深奥的话
So profound for one who's nine, don't you think?
-这也许是家族遗传 -肯定是了
- But then, I guess it runs in the family. - it must.
西弗太太 获得普利策文学奖有何感想？
Tell me, Mrs. Seaver, what does it feel like to win the Pulitzer Prize for Literature?
朱丽叶，坦白说.
Well, I'll be honest with you, Juliet.
感觉挺好的
It feels good.
开心极了
Darn good.
只是开头几次得奖才开心
The first couple of times, anyway.
西弗先生，米克说你是一名画家
And, Mr. Seaver, Mikhail tells me you're a painter.
请问你用什么颜料？
Do you work in oils or acrylic?
一般是乳胶漆.
Mostly flat latex...
有时也会用瓷漆
and some high-gloss enamel.
要看看我最新的作品吗？
Would you like to see one of my recent works?
我称之为“楼上的厕所”
I call it, "Upstairs Bathroom."
爸爸，今天可没时间欣赏了
Dad, no! Maybe some other time.
西弗先生，你是否受了.
Mr. Seaver, tell me, have you been influenced...
最近德国的抽象表现主义的影响？
by the recent wave of German abstract expressionists?
不，影响我最多的还是荷兰派
No. I'm really more influenced by the Dutch Boys.
你是说伦布兰特和佛梅尔？ [荷兰著名画家]
Oh, you mean Rembrandt and Vermeer.
这太有意思了 因为你和毕加索是一脉相承的
Well, that's fascinating, considering you we're a student of Picasso's.
妈妈，我想起来了.
Which reminds me, Mom....
毕加索叔叔今年不是要来度假吗？
Is Uncle Pablo coming to visit for the holidays this year?
麦克，毕加索死了
Mike, Picasso is dead.
这样，他也许不会来了
Well, I guess that's a no.
毕加索就喜欢我们的黑色幽默
Yeah, Uncle Pablo loved it when we joked this way about death.
死亡又是什么？
Yes, but what is death?
太深奥了
Oh, you are so deep.
-有时候吓着我了 -谢谢
- Sometimes it even scares me. - Thank you.
能遇到你们的家庭.
You know, it really is extraordinary...
真是太不寻常了
meeting a family like you in a place like this.
- Oh? - Oh?
还以为只有在城里才能享受 这么高雅的夜晚
I mean, I thought I'd have to go into the city to find a cultural evening like this.
因为乡下人都文盲
Because Lord knows that most suburbanites are brain dead.
米克，我想起来了.
Which reminds me, Mishka...
你能不能陪我进城.
I was wondering if you'd like to come to the city with me...
去欣赏戏剧艺术
to see some performance art.
麦克，去吧，因为这里乡下地方.
Oh, go, Mike. No, go, go. Because Lord knows...
确实没有戏剧艺术可言
you can't get a decent piece of performance art in the suburbs.
真是迫不及待呢
Yeah, you know, that really burns me up.
明天是哥哈特的最后一场演出
Tomorrow is the last night of Gerhardts performance piece.
我希望你能陪我去看
And there's no one I'd rather see it with than you.
好吧，一言为定
Well, then, it's a date.
-麦克 -怎么了？
- Mike. - Yeah, Mom?
你忘了？
Aren't you forgetting something?
是啊，原来的安排，也是明天晚上
Yeah, a prior commitment, like something else for tomorrow night?
对家庭来说是件重大的事
One that's very, very important to your entire family?
明晚并没有什么安排吧
Gee, no, I don't think I had any plans for tomorrow night.
肯定有，我们要.
Sure you do, Mike. We're supposed to go--
米克，他在干什么？
Mishka, what is he doing?
他在跳舞
He's dancing.
匪夷所思的是 这位哲学家也喜欢现代舞蹈
Yes, incredibly enough, little Ben, here, is a philosopher and a modern dancer.
明晚他要表演
Now, he's got a recital tomorrow night...
不过哲学家跳舞嘛.
but once you've seen one little philosopher dance...
都是一个样的
you've seen them all.
那我们说定了
So, we're on?
是的，驷马难追
Right, we're on.
米克，再见
Au revoir, Mishka.
真是有气质
Hey, was she incredible, or what, huh?
我知道.
I know, I know.
很抱歉，我不能出席保龄球赛
Look, I'm sorry I had to pass on the bowling...
你们能体谅我的
but I knew you guys would understand.
不体谅？
You don't understand.
不原谅？
You really don't understand.
麦克，你答应过的，你一定要去
Mike, you have to go with us. You promised.
没有你，我们怎么能打败库斯曼家？
How are we supposed to beat the Koosmans without you?
不就是一场球赛吗？
You guys, it's just a game.
问题不在这，你许下了承诺
That's not the point, Mike. You made a commitment.
我们都依靠你了
We're all counting on you.
如果家人都不可靠，还能靠谁？
And if you can't count on your family, who can you count on?
爸爸，我交到朋友了
Look, Dad, I'm involved in a relationship here.
而且是艺术家
With an artist.
我怎能放弃机会去打球呢？
I can't just drop that to go bowling.
朋友？
A relationship?
她对你一无所知 她还以为你叫“米克”
She doesn't even know who you are. She thinks you're "Mishka."
其实你和我们一样，打保龄球的
And you're just a bowler like the rest of us.
你怎么知道我会没出息？
Hey, how do you know what I am?
说不定我不是打保龄球的 说不定我就是“米克”
Maybe I'm not a bowler. Maybe I am Mishka.
我快吐了
Maybe I'm gonna barf.
若在旧时代，他早被枪毙了
If this we're the Russian Army, he'd be tried for desertion and shot.
凯罗，牛不喝水按不下牛头
Carol, we're not going to force your brother to go bowling with us.
不过我有预感 他很快会意识到自己不是“米克”
Anyway, I have a hunch that pretty soon he'll realize he's not Mishka.
我算什么？我只是个油漆匠
But what do I know? I'm just a painter.
“牛的精髓”
"Essence of Cow? "
-真是杰作 -这个，我很喜爱
- What a piece of-- - This? I love this.
是啊，我也很喜爱
Oh, yes. Yes, I love this thing.
牛我见过，不过没这个牛
I mean, I haven't seen cow essence before, but this....
-安德雷，费比兹奥 -朱丽叶!
- Andre! Fabrizzio! - Oh, Juliet!
哥特勒的画展后，我们还没见过呢
God, I haven't seen you since the Gertrude Stein-a-thon.
这是我的好朋友麦克.西弗 麦克是一名诗人
This is a good friend of mine, Michael Seaver. Michael is a poet.
表演快要开始了
Oh, look, the performance piece is about to start.
听说很棒呢
Oh, I hear it's brilliant.
-猩猩对着阳光.. -在吠叫
- Orangutans bark at the sound of.... - Sunlight.
-为什么没有.. -木材
- Why are there no.... - Lumberjacks....
-在城市里？ -大城市
- In big cities? - Big cities.
太棒了!精彩!
Brilliant! Absolutely brilliant!
这是对美国中产阶级的时尚 和缺陷的.
It's a perfect commentary...
最好的抨击
on the fashions and foibles of middle-class America.
是的，当然是的
Oh, yes, yes, absolutely.
时尚还有缺陷
Fashions and foibles.
米克，说笑吧？
Oh, Mishka, you can't be serious.
这显然是对解除核子武器的呼吁
I mean, it's obviously a plea for nuclear disarmament.
显然是解除核子武器
Obviously. Yes, nuclear disarmament.
这都看不出来就真是傻瓜了
You'd have to be dumb as a post to miss that.
那么这是对时尚.
So you're saying it's a comment on contemporary fashions...
还有对核武器的抨击？
and nuclear disarmament?
对，是的
Yes. Yes, right.
对，大家都知道，现在的时尚是.
I mean, everybody knows that contemporary fashions are...
核子武器
obviously nuclear.
所以要解除
And that's disarming.
好了，队员们，出发!
All right, team, et's go!
-一起喊“S”!
-“S” - Give me an "S"! - "S."
-一起喊“E!”
-“E” - Give me an "E"! - "E."
好吧，我自己来
All right, I'll finish it myself.
-“AVER!”什么单词？ -“输定了”!
- A-V-E-R! What does it spell? - Losers.
拜托，虽然主力队员不在.
No, come on. Now, maybe we've lost one of our stronger team members...
但我们相信还是会赢
but we've gotta believe we're gonna win.
为什么相信我们会赢？
And we do believe we're gonna win. And why do we believe we're gonna win?
因为我们是白痴
Because we're idiots?
不，因为我们是.
No, Ben. Because we're...
“西弗保龄球队”!
"The Bowlin Seavers."
怎么看？瞧瞧
What do you think? Look at this.
-“西弗高人”？ -还不止呢
- "Jason "Bud" Seaver"? - And that's not all.
还有一件.
I also have one here...
“西弗牛人”
for Ben "Fudd" Seaver.
还有“西弗迷人”
For Carol "Spud" Seaver.
好玩吧？
Isn't this fun?
还有你的“西弗狂人”
And Maggie "Mud" Seaver.
“狂人”？
Mud?
我再也想不出什么花哨词儿了
Well, there aren't that many words that end in "ud."
准备好没？
Okay, we ready?
-一起喊“S”!
-“S”! - Now, give me an "S"! - "S! "
-一起喊“E”!
-“E”! - Give me an "E"! - "E! "
-一起喊“A”!
-“A”! - Give me an "A"! - "A! "
-一起喊“V”!
-“V”! - Give me a "V"! - "V! "
-一起喊“E”!
-“E”! - Give me an "E"! - "E! "
-一起喊“R”!
-“R”! - Give me an "R"! - "R! "
-什么单词？ -“输定了”!
- What do you got? - Losers!
麦克，说说你的作品吧
So, Michael, why don't we talk about your work?
麦克那天念了一首很棒的诗
Michael read the most remarkable poem the other day.
这只是我最近学习新象征主义的作品
It was just a little something from my recent neo-symbolist period.
是吗？之前你是什么流派的？
Really? What we're you before you became a neo-symbolist?
之前是.
I was...
新橡皮主义!
a Neo-Synephrine!
他是说笑!真有意思!
Oh, a joke! How funny!
麦克，现在就朗诵一首诗吧!
Well, Michael, why don't you read one of your poems for us now?
立刻来
Yes, now. Right now.
大家好，我要介绍麦克.西弗 优秀的.
Everybody, I'd like to introduce Michael Seaver. An exciting--
-不行 -为什么？
- Juliet, I can't do that. - Why not?
稿子没带来
I didn't even bring my poem.
那又怎样？以前的作品随便来一首
So what? Why don't you recite one of your older works?
我实在朗诵不出来
No, actually, I couldn't do that.
麦克，这什么意思？
What are you talking about, Michael?
朱丽叶，这是法律问题
Look, Juliet, it's this legal thing.
我把诗歌都卖给好莱坞了
I mean, I sold all my poems to Hollywood...
现在只有杰克.尼科尔森才有权朗读
and from now on only Jack Nicholsons allowed to read them.
米克，你就别打趣了 快来一首
Oh, Mishka, stop joking around and read your poem.
-大家都在等 -朱丽叶.
- Everybody's waiting. - Look, look, Juliet.
-我有话要说 -什么？
- I have to tell you something. - What?
-老实说我不是诗人 -什么？
- The truth is, I'm not a poet. - What?
-那你念的诗..？ -不是我写的，买来的
- But the poem you read, it was-- - I didn't write it. I bought it.
你是说你骗了我？
You mean you lied to me?
朱丽叶，你一走进教室.
Look, Juliet, when you first walked into that classroom...
我就知道你兴众不同
I thought you we're so much different, so much classier...
比任何人都更高贵，我只是想讨好你
than anyone else I'd ever seen. I just wanted to impress you.
但你家人，普利策文学奖，现代舞蹈.
But your family, the Pulitzer Prize, the modern dance recital--
我家里人并不是什么现代舞者
No, no. My family's not at a modern dance recital.
-那这是干嘛？ -保龄球!
- Then what was this? - Bowling!
-保龄球 -对了，保龄球
- Bowling. - Yeah, bowling.
这是我们和邻居一年一度的比赛
See, it's this big match we have every year with the neighbors.
叫做“保龄球大餐比赛”
It's called "Bowling for Dinners."
这是我爸的主意
That was my dad's idea.
谁输了.
And the losers have to take the winners out...
就要到费博餐厅请吃一顿大鱼大肉
for a big surf 'n' turf dinner at Ferber's House of Meat and Fish.
费博餐厅，大鱼大肉？
Ferber's House of Meat and Fish?
-什么？ -真恶心
- What? - Well, it's such a disgusting image.
两家人打保龄球争肉吃
I mean, two entire families rolling balls for meat.
还有蔬菜，米饭和马铃薯!
Hey, it comes with a salad and choice of rice or potato, okay?
真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
你是打保龄球的.
You're one of those people who bowls...
逛商店的.
and hangs out at malls...
吃热狗的土包子
and eats hot dogs on a stick.
我就是这样，有什么不好？
Yeah, I guess I am. So what's wrong with that?
我喜欢逛商店，喜欢保龄球
Maybe I like malls. Maybe I like bowling.
-麦克，小声点 -干嘛了？我很丢脸是吧？
- Michael, will you please lower your voice. - What? Are you ashamed of me, Juliet?
我让你丢脸了？
You ashamed of being seen here with me?
真是难为情
This is really embarrassing.
丢脸？我教你丢脸？
Oh, you want embarrassing? I'll give you embarrassing.
老兄，想知道大城市里 为什么没有木材吗？
Hey, buddy, you want to know why theres no lumberjacks in the big cities?
因为木材都被削成热狗棍子了
It's because they're all at the malls eating hot dogs on sticks!
-完了 -死定了
- It's over. - We're dead.
前途渺茫
It's hopeless.
这么泄气，才输了两场
Now come on, guys, we've only lost two games!
一共才打了两场
We've only played two games.
恨死库斯曼一家了
I hate the Koosmans.
听到了吗，他们已经在吧台唱到.
Did you hear them over there? They had the whole snack bar singing:
★“西弗老弟，名誉扫地”
"We're mopping the floor with the Seaver Four."
连上厕所都这么唱
I won't even tell you what they have them singing in the men's room.
咱练习练习，可以做到的
Well, then, et's practice. Come on, Carol, you can do it.
拿起球，练练出球
et's just grab a ball right now, work on your approach a little bit.
记住绷紧肩膀，臀部和手腕.
Just remember to square your shoulders and whip that wrist...
接着送出去，加油!
and follow through. Okay? Come on.
-打到8分! -对了
- I got eight pins! - Yes.
按规则来说.
Well, I'll have to check the rule book on this...
打到别人的道上没分
but I'm pretty sure they have to be in our lane.
这一顿可要破费了
Well, this will be an expensive dinner this year.
库斯曼一家决定不减肥了
The Koosmans are off their diet.
该死的
The slobs.
对不起，我迟到了
Hi, guys. Sorry, I'm late.
麦克
Mike.
关于我的所作所为.
Hey, look, guys, about the way I've been acting....
不知道该怎么说了
I don't know how to say this, but....
-我欠大家一个道歉 -麦克
- Well, I guess I owe you guys.... - Hey, Mike.
爸爸
Yeah, Dad.
要打球还是要写诗？
Do you want to bowl or are you gonna write a poem about it?
我要打球
I'm gonna bowl.
那就赶快练习
And you better hurry, too. Better bowl fast, Michael.
好的，来了
All right, here we go.
米克!
Hey, Mishka!
★我们得第一!
We're number one! Yes!
大家听好了.
All right, all right, attention, please.
我现在代表西弗全家.
On behalf of the entire Seaver family...
我代表“牛人”，“狂人”，“迷人” “强人”和我本人“高人”.
I'm talking about Fudd, Spud, Mud, and of course myself, Bud...
把这个颁发给使我们胜利的人
may I present this to the man who led us to victory.
我看还是家里人对我最了解
Well, I guess when all's said and done, it's your family who knows you best.
“超人”西弗
"Mike 'Stud' Seaver."
[zeroxia@gmail.com] 2006.03.12